sexbankroll.com 2009-06-19

# Sexbankroll.com - Are you ready to roll?

This website (the "Site") is licensed to **Safe Dock Capital Limited, Safe Dock Capital S.A., PV Key Punch S.L.**

Our postal address is   

Safe Dock Capital Limited   
Ingles Manor, Castle Hill Avenue Folkstone  
CT20 2RD Kent   
United Kingdom 

Safe Dock Capital Limited  
Amory Building  
Victoria Road  
Basseterre, St. Kitts  
St. Kitts and Nevis  
East Caribbean 

Safe Dock Capital S.A.,  
Forum, Ed. E., Santa Ana, San Jose  
POBox: 10881-1000 San Jose, Costa Rica 

PV Key Punch S.L., Spain  
C/Sant Miquel, 30 - 3 L  
07002-Palma de Mallorca (Spain)   

We can be reached via e-mail at [websupport@sexbankroll.com](mailto:websupport@sexbankroll.com)

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding subscribers and members of this Site. This is an adult Site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. 

This Site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. 

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE. 

NOTICE - USE OF THIS WEBSITE BY THE MEMBER CONSTITUTES THE EXPRESS CONSENT OF THE MEMBER TO THE USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY SITE IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY. 

**_What Information About Members is Collected?_**

Prior to acceptance as a Member or Subscriber of this Site, consumers will be required to provide certain personal as well as demographic information which may include, but is not necessarily limited to, the Member's name, address, birthday, e-mail address, gender, marital status, occupation, education, credit card number and expiration date of the credit card, username and password, and special interests or affiliations. This Site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database. 

If the Site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a Member of the Site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the Member voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the Site and included in its customer database. 

When a Member of this Site requests webpages from the Site's server or clicks on banners or other hypertext links, the Site will automatically collect some information or data about the Member, including the Member's IP address, the information that is collected may also indicate any special preferences or requests of the Member; all that information and data will be collected by the Site and included in its customer database. 

If a Member sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database. 

The Site may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behavior of Members by the use of "cookies"or other programming means - any information about Members collected by the Site through the use of cookies or other programming means may be included in its customer database. 

You may obtain further information about "cookies" and how they function at: [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

**_Use of Personal Member Information._**

By the Member's use of the Site, the Member expressly agrees that the Site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about Members that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties to send you email notifications, newsletters, promos and any other offers that Safe Dock Capital SA and third parties wish to send. 

Please note that personal information about a Member may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the Site. 

The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a Member may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the Site. This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites. 

Whenever applicable, each Member should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Site. 

**_Security of Personal Information Collected by the Site._**

Consistent with the Policies set forth in this Privacy Statement, the Site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to Members that is collected by the Site. 

All Members should consider any information provided to or collected by the Site as **non-confidential** , and consequently the Site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any Member is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient. 

**_"OPT-IN" and "OPT-OUT" Provisions._**

There may be occasions when a Member will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the Site or from third-party service or content providers, which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers"). 

"OPT-IN" -- Some Offers may be presented to the Member with the option to express the subsciber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes" the Member indicates that the Member "OPTS-IN" to that Offer and thereby agrees and assents that the Member's personal information and data may be disclosed to third-parties. 

"OPT-OUT" -- Other Offers may be presented with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the Member does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the Offer) then the Site may transfer the Member's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the Offer. If the Member deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the Member may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider. 

**_"OPT-OUT" Revocation Procedure._**

The Site also offers all Members a procedure for "Opting-Out" if the Member subsequently chooses to revoke any consent to receive Offers by sending an e-mail to [websupport@sexbankroll.com](mailto:websupport@sexbankroll.com), clearly stating that the Member has revoked consent to receive any future Offers. 

**_Data Controller._**

The Data Controller for all personal information collected about Members of the site can be reached by e-mail at [websupport@sexbankroll.com](mailto:websupport@sexbankroll.com). The Data Controller has the authority to resolve all issues regarding the collection, modification, correction, deletion and use of the personal information that has been collected by the Site. 

**_Review of Personal Information by Member/Means of Challenging Data._**

A Member to this Site can review any personal information collected by the Site relating to that Member by sending an e-mail to the Site's DATA CONTROLLER at [websupport@sexbankroll.com](mailto:websupport@sexbankroll.com), clearly stating that the Member wishes to review the Member's personal information which has been collected by the Site. 

The individual Member shall have the following rights with respect to any personal information gathered by the Site: 

  * to obtain from a data controller, or otherwise, confirmation of whether or not the data controller has data relating to him;  

  * to have communicated to him, data relating to him within a reasonable time; at a charge, if any, that is not excessive; in a reasonable manner; and in a form that is readily intelligible to him;   

  * to be given reasons if a request made under subparagraphs(a) and (b) is denied, and to be able to challenge such denial; and   

  * to challenge data relating to him and, if the challenge is successful to have the data erased, rectified, completed or amended. 

**_Terms and Conditions of Membership._**

Each Member should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of Membership of this Site. By accepting membership to this Site you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this Site to use information that it has gathered from Members. 

In the event of any conflicts between the Membership Terms the Conditions and this Privacy Policy Statement, the provisions of this Privacy Policy shall control.
